#### **RESUME**

#### Shaika sameena

Cell No: +91-7330637635

Email Id: shaikasameena77@gmail.com

## **CAREER OBJECTIVE:**

Enthusiastic customer service representative with experience working with international customer base. Trained in project and time management with extensive knowledge at service delivery and proven multitasking abilities. Committed to maintaining professional relationships with clients and customers to increase profitability and drive business result.

## **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATIONS:-**

- **MBA: Finance & Marketing** from Hyderabad Presidency College Osmania University.
- Bachelor of Commerce: Computers from MS Degree College Osmania University.

### **SKILLS:-**

- Quality assurance
- Self-direction
- Documentation and reporting
- Customer Relationship Management
- ❖ Account Management
- Client Communication

## **EXPERIENCE:-**

## Senior Customer Happiness Officer | Neeman's

Hyderabad - August 2021 - till date

#### Roles and Responsibilities:-

- ❖ Helped large volume of customers every day with positive attitude and focus on customer satisfaction.
- \* Responded to customer emails and chats to answer questions about products and services.
- ❖ Informed customers about special promotions and provided detailed information for various products.
- ❖ Offered advice and assistance to customers, paying attention to special needs or wants.
- ❖ Maintained customer satisfaction with forward-thinking strategies focused on addressing customer needs and resolving concerns.
- Utilized internal software and tools to meet customer needs and resolved issues promptly.
- Increased revenue by cross-selling and up-selling products and services.
- Provided customer feedback to management and identified areas of improvement for products and services.
- ❖ Actively listened to customers, handled concerns quickly and escalated major issues to supervisor.
- ❖ Provided training and support to new associates to help provide high-quality customer service.
- ❖ Kept detailed records of customer interactions to track and resolve issues quickly.

Contd...2...

- ❖ Managed timely and effective replacement of damaged or missing products.
- ❖ Educated customers about billing, payment processing and support policies and procedures.
- ❖ Collaborated with sales team members to stay current on inventory levels, complete accurate orders, and resolve item issues.
- Delivered prompt service to prioritize customer needs.
- ❖ Increased efficiency and team productivity by promoting operational best practices.

## Senior Customer Care Executive | Seminole Electronics ( MIVI )

Hyderabad - January 2019 - July 2021

# Roles and Responsibilities:-

- \* Responded to customer needs through competent customer service and prompt problem-solving.
- \* Resolved concerns with products or services to help with retention and drive sales.
- \* Recommended, selected and helped locate and obtain out-of-stock product based on customer requests.
- ❖ Collaborated with staff members to enhance customer service experience and exceed team goals through effective client satisfaction rates.
- ❖ Provided excellent customer care by responding to requests, assisting with product selection and handling ordering functions.
- \* Trained new personnel regarding company operations, policies and services.

## Senior Customer Care Representative | ESMSYS

Hyderabad - May 2015 - February 2018

## Roles and Responsibilities:-

- ❖ Helped large volume of customers every day with positive attitude and focus on customer satisfaction.
- ❖ Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints quickly.
- ❖ Delivered exceptional customer service to every customer by leveraging extensive knowledge of products and services and creating welcoming, positive experiences via email and calls.
- \* Reminding customers about the appointments and sharing all the necessary information for a smoother process.
- ❖ Analyzed customer feedback for process improvements to achieve long-term business objectives.
- ❖ Managed supplier deliveries around client needs to increase client retention.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS:-**

- Basic Knowledge of computer.
- \* MS Office.

#### **DECLARATION:-**

I do hereby declare that the above details are correct to my best of my knowledge.

Date:

Place: Hyderabad.

(Shaika Sameena)